在上一课中，我们学习了如何将数字图像导入计算机，我们学到了很多东西
In the last lecture we learned how to import a digital image into a computer and we learned
计算机内的图像只是一大堆数字。更确切地说，它是
that an image inside a computer is just a big bunch of numbers. More precisely it's
一个矩形的数字数组，我们可以认为它是一个矩阵。现在得到图像
a rectangular array of numbers which we can consider to be a matrix. Now getting the image
进入电脑只是第一步。我们需要以各种方式操纵这个图像
into the computer is just the first step. We need to manipulate this image in various
方法，以便我们可以从该图像中提取足以提供的信息
ways so that we can extract the information from that image which is sufficient to hand
穿过一个机器人，让它完成它的工作。所以在这个讲座和下一个讲座中，我们都是
across to a robot to allow it to do its job. So in this lecture and the next one, we're
去了解一些转换图像的基本方法，以帮助我们
going to learn about some fundamental ways to transform images so as to help us in the
提取意义的过程。
process of extracting meaning.
这些技术属于一种称为图像处理的类别，这就是我们的方式
These techniques fall into a category which is called image processing, which is how we
拍摄一张图像并将其转换为不同的图像，这有助于我们完成提取任务
take one image and transform it into a different image which helps us in our task of extracting
那个意思。所以我们有兴趣考虑的各种转换
that meaning. So the sorts of transformations that we would be interested in considering
是;我们如何增强图像的对比度？我们如何降低分辨率
are; how do we enhance the contrast of an image? How do we reduce the resolution of
一个图像？我们如何突出显示图像中的水平线条或如何突出显示垂直线条
an image? How do we highlight horizontal lines in an image or how do we highlight vertical
图像中的线条？或者我们如何突出显示红色或绿色或者绿色的东西
lines in an image? Or how do we highlight things that are red or that are green or that
是蓝色的。所以这些是一些基本技术，可以帮助我们完成装备之旅
are blue. So these are some fundamental techniques that will help us in our journey of equipping
有远见的机器人。
robots with vision.